What do you think the power of God is? A
charm?
Do you know what it means to stand and
speak over God's people and the God of
the universe begins to honor your
speakings? Now, I hope you know
I hope you know not to sound proud. God
is not a man. Burn that in your spirit.
God is not a man.
You want to speak over a man's life? Let
the gates of your destiny be open and
then it is open.
Do you know the kind of sacrifice? This
is the point I want us to get. Ladies
and gentlemen, so I I really hate
sharing my story because most times
um it doesn't achieve what I wanted to
achieve. It just looks like we're just
marketing ourselves and and you know,
acting arrogant. But I wish I had the
liberty to share with you the instances
of the sacrifices that this man before
you has made. It would be evil for you
to believe what is happening is just
luck.
I repeat, it would be evil for I don't
care whoever to believe that what you
see today is luck. No.
There are names.
There are titles.
There are legends and tales of strength.
But only Yeshua
will reign forever.
To his kingdom, there'll be no end.
There are names.
There are titles.
There are legends and tales of strength.
Only Ashua
will reign forever.
To his kingdom, there'll be no end.
Hear me.
You want a generation to hear your voice
is more than posting videos on social
media. Now, I'm saying this respectfully
speaking. I want to help my precious
generation get out of that garbage and
invest in the spirit. It takes more than
just telling people I am here. There is
a track record in the spirit. Let me
tell you. If heaven does not sign upon
your life, you will waste your time for
nothing upon the earth. You believe that
people will just come and give you
finances like that? Everybody will not
dash you. You have to understand the
financial system of the kingdom. God can
raise men to support you, but you
believe that men will be the ones to run
your your life financially. Go and find
out how finances work.
And bring rest to your life once and for
all.
The anointing, you need to go and stay
with God. Find out the various wells in
the spirit and the skill to fetch and
draw from them. Mhm.
Not every well works the same way.
Just because you learned how to fetch
from a particular well, the Bible says
wells of salvation.
There are different skills to fetch.
So, you will see people who are
operating at different frequencies in
the spirit. It's because they have
mastered how to draw from the spirit.
Hallelujah.
The sacrifice of fasting,
the sacrifice of prayer,
the sacrifice of honoring the voice of
God even at your inconvenience.
I cannot have told you I don't know how
many times God has given me painful
instructions. Give this, empty this, do
this, and sometimes it does not make
sense.
I shared with you my story last year
when God gave an instruction to sow a
seed.
I knew that a season was coming and God
was opening me up. It was a new
dimension in the spirit. I've taught you
how to discern when seasons come to an
end.
An unusual desire to pray, an unusual
desire to give, unusual attack from the
kingdom of darkness. These are signs
that tell you a season is coming to an
end.
You don't want to be around people
again. Something just isolate you to be
alone is because the master wants to
speak to you. And if you don't
understand these writings, you will keep
wasting your time. There are things God
will never tell you in public.
You need to painfully know how to stay
alone, then his voice comes.
Hallelujah. And God gave me an
instruction.
First, to bring a serious seed as a
ministry and to sow. That seed itself
was I can tell you sincerely at any
level it will touch you.
And then
then came the bigger instruction. And
I'm saying this because I want you to
understand. It's not to brag at all.
God now told me that what I told the
ministry to give, you give twice that
amount.
When you give Ishmael,
you can drive him in one day, go away.
But when God says to give Isaac,
it will touch you. Isaac will touch you.
Isaac ba will touch you.
But you see, I've worked with God a bit
and I know that every time God says open
your hand, it's not because of what is
there. It's about It's because of what
he's bringing.
And with that sacrifice
I I rejoiced in my pain
as I honored God. God forbid that he
will speak and I will not listen to him.
Ladies and gentlemen, the rest is
history.
Another dimension opened for me that
till forever
Listen, people do not just rise.
The sacrifice of paying the price to
build. Are you willing to go through it?
For someone God can just call you and
say every night for the next 3 months, I
want to meet with you 12:00 to 3:00. It
is me and you alone. That is my covenant
for the next 3 months. It may not be for
everybody, but it's part of the
preparation to birth and You may even be
a businessman. That's what will surprise
you. I say, "God, go and talk to them up
close one and the rest and leave me in
peace. I thought you would teach me how
to make money." He's preparing you
because when those billions come demons
will say, "Where did the money go to?"
And they will follow your business and
say, "We are here." The king of Tyre
just found out that something left
heaven and did not pass through him to
you. And so they will have to come and
vet.
And so God can tell a businessman, "For
3 months you are not talking money with
God.
You are fasting and praying and building
capacity. Afterwards, a door of business
will open and by the time people think
you are just wearing suit and tie, they
do not know that by sacrifice you
brought yourself into the fivefold
ministry."
Ladies and gentlemen, I want to show you
what separates men from boys.
There are many people who do not want to
pay the price. It is a language that our
ignorant, sadly, and arrogant generation
does not want to hear. Sharp sharp
everything.
It is only God that will tell you the
amount of times I've finished this Bible
you are seeing. My former Bible, you
open it and you would think
there's writing everywhere. Sometimes I
would write
all kinds of things there because you
are studying to show yourself approved.
That's why you see me quote scriptures
and I can tell you what another version
says. You try it if you think it's a
gift.
It's not You know, we have this idea
that God just magically endowed you. No.
The grace I'm not downplaying the grace
of God. I hope you get what I'm saying.
You want to command power, authority
over nations, you are going to have to
stay with God. Are you ready to invest
in with the spirit? You don't have a
track record with the Holy Ghost. Listen
to me. You come out like this just
playing games and for show, you will
only embarrass yourself for nothing.
It says, "But I know whom I have
believed."
You came here tonight
not just to meet God alone, but you came
here to meet men whose blood are
dripping upon the altar.
He said, "Let no man trouble me, for I
bear upon my body there is a scar that
the realm of the spirit knows. Jesus I
know. Paul I know. Joshua Selman I know.
You It's with blood you sign that
signature."
He that cometh unto God must come
believing that he is the rewarder.
While you are fasting, you know the
rewarder is watching you.
While you are praying, the rewarder is
watching you.
Somebody says,
"Come and bribe and become a director."
And you say, "No." And for that reason,
your children pay the price for 1 year.
The rewarder is watching.
Can I tell you?
If you do not know the rewarder,
compromise will look pleasant.
all these cutting corners in ministry,
you can stay, even if it's with five
people, with joy. I know the rewarder is
watching. You are training the five
people as if you are preaching in a
stadium, mentoring them. Because those
five people are not your members. They
are your leaders you are training. When
your leaders are trained, members can
now come.
Are we together?
Yes.
Development is difficult. It took Jesus
18 years to be ready for ministry. 18, 1
8. 18 years of actively building
himself.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's time for us to throw away premature
manifestation and premature exposure and
get back to the place where men are
made, made for their destinies. Are we
together now? The stage is not for
rehearsal. The stage is for
manifestation. If you want to rehearse,
go to the wilderness. You will be given
a chance to kill the lion. Don't come
and stand before Goliath to try. Trial
and error will destroy you. Goliath is
not playing games.
Learn with the lion. Learn with the bear
and master the art of war. When you
stand before Goliath, it is one one
opportunity to bring him down.
Amen.
Listen,
you must master the mysteries of the
presence of God.
You must master the mysteries of the
anointing. You must master the mystery
of dominion. You must master the
mysteries of influence. You must master
the mysteries of the word of God.
People will not just come and listen to
you like that. Business man, what have
you read about business?
Do you know the best people in your
industry? Have you humbled yourself to
learn from them? Or you are wallowing in
the pride of saying everybody is a
colleague. Run away from colleague
mentality. That's what has kept many
people down in this our arrogant
generation. Just because great men are
humble does not mean they are stupid.
Know where you stand and draw the line
with honor.
No matter how humble our fathers are,
sometimes a particular father of faith,
I will not mention the name, but when we
have the privilege of talking, sometimes
he can say, "Ah,
you know I'm speaking to an apostle
now." And I just laugh. I say, "Ah,
daddy, don't don't say that. Oh, he's
still your boy." And we're laughing.
Most of you, as they say that kind of
thing, you carry it as a compliment.
That a pastor is speaking to an apostle.
What what what foolish indoctrination.
These are men who their tears move
heaven. And heaven will say, "Who is
making you cry?"
Is someone learning?
You own a school. It's time to stop
clapping for yourself and sit down. How
can I make it the best? How can this be
the greatest? You own a business. You
are in ministry. It's time to stop You
You cannot be going up and down every
every program every show you are there.
Jumping from pillar to post and you want
the anointing to work in your life? No.
Samuel was called a seer. You didn't see
him out every time, but when Samuel came
out, people would know that God is about
to say something because this guy has
come out. Most of us have cheapened
ourselves because you are everywhere
doing everything.
Hallelujah. When others are sleeping,
you wake up in the night. Father, for
the sake of my destiny, I love you, but
you are a rewarder. I came from a family
where no one has risen and I heard my
parents tell me that they tried. I have
made up my mind that I will be that
savior. Lord, for the next 7 months, it
is 2 hours with you every night. Zakus
katabrakata. While you are doing that,
you are in your small room. Don't worry,
the rewarder is watching.
The rewarder is watching.
I sense in my spirit that God gave me
this message because in this season, the
rewarder is going to move again.
Move from family to family. Move from
ministry to ministry.
There are some of you, hear me. You have
served for a very long time and it looks
like nobody has noticed you. I'm telling
you prophetically, do not feel bad. I'm
saying this by the spirit of the living
God. The rewarder is going to have a
convocation and say, "I remember you
paid the school fees of a young man in
2015. Nobody saw you to say thank you,
but I have come as a rewarder that your
children will never beg again because of
what you have done."
Hear me.
When God wants to schedule a season of
reward,
the first thing he does
is to put something in your hand. Exodus
chapter 4.
Give it to us, please.
Exodus 4 and verse 2.
I hope I got that right.
Yes. This was the encounter. Exodus 4
and verse 2. And the Lord said unto
Moses,
"What is that that is in your hand?"
There is always something in your hand
that will be used to make your
influence. Moses, you're about to be
greatly magnified by God. That rod. And
when you read the verses after he said
to throw that rod on the ground, you
must cast that rod and worship God with
it.
Until that rod is handed over to God to
refine it. Now, go to verse 17. Same
Exodus 4 and verse 17. He said, "Thou
shalt take this rod in your hand,
wherewith thou shalt do signs." It was
your rod before, but nothing was upon it
to do signs. Same rod. Now, with the
anointing upon it, you can do signs.
Same gift of singing.
Sometimes I watch this my precious
people as they worship, as they sing.
And all the the lovely people who just
sang, and I'm looking at them. And, you
know, I keep praying that God will grant
them the grace to keep building.
Because, you see, the value of the
anointing is that it comes upon a
prepared vessel. Let me say it again.
The value of the anointing is that it
comes upon a prepared vessel. When God
calls you, he files you before anointing
you. Most people want the anointing to
come upon the unrefined version of them.
While you wait for power,
make sure you tarry in Jerusalem
praying.
While you wait for power, make sure you
are not idle. Keep working on your
leadership skills. While you wait for
the anointing, keep working on your
human relation skills. While you wait
for the anointing, keep working to
understand the dynamics of ministry.
While you wait for the anointing, keep
studying to be an excellent preacher.
While you wait for the anointing, you
want to become a leader par excellence,
you want to become an educator, you want
to become a business person. While you
wait for the anointing, don't sit down
and fold your arms. Wake up in the
night, buy the books, go online. Don't
watch nonsense. Go online, find valuable
materials that relate to your destiny.
All those exercises, are you preparing
for the ministry of the rewarder? But I
can tell you, the rewarder will always
come.
That's why you find out that ordinary
men get to seasons where it looks like
God just gives them visibility, and then
we erroneously say they came from
nowhere. There is nobody who comes out
from nowhere. No.
Hallelujah.
Today I look at what God has graciously
done in my life, and I'm truly humbled.
My prayer is that God will use my life
to inspire a generation, more than just
planting pride, to help people know that
spending time to market yourself is a
total waste of time. Your marketing is
to build your value. I'm saying this
because something is going to come on
someone shortly. I'm going to pray some
prayers for you and for your destiny.
There are doors, remember we're dealing
with opening of doors. He said, "The
gift of a man makes room for him."
So, when it's time for God to end the
cycle of poverty in your family, it's
not just the Esther anointing he's going
to drop. Before the Esther anointing
arrives, listen carefully, he will now
isolate at least one person who begins
to get angry with that situation and
say, "Lord, things cannot continue like
this. We can't continue living from hand
to mouth. Our daughters and our sons
will not keep prostituting themselves
because they are looking for money.
Lord, I will learn God's way of doing
this. And God will plant a passion in
that person, and he will begin to listen
to tapes and teachings. The rewarder is
watching. Remember,
the more he's building himself, the more
she's building herself, enduring the
temptation for all kinds of compromises,
preparing yourself for a great life. And
after 10 years,
the person will be running an
organization that is multi-billion, and
people will say, "I used to know you."
You are right, but not that version
anymore.
Not that version anymore.
Can I tell you?
When it has to do with refining your
potentials,
so that you schedule the seasons of
reward, don't spare yourself. Don't let
your tears We live in a generation that
is excessively obsessed with comfort. We
love comfort too much. Listen, comfort
is when you have arrived, not when you
are starting.
A young man is about to start life, and
he wants a comfort of a veteran. He sits
down with a 50, 60, 70-year-old man, and
he wants the same kind of treatment.
No, sir.
Apostle, I got a job. They are just
giving me 50,000, and I have to trek for
30 minutes. Go and ask parents who trek
from one community to one community to
go to a a secondary school. For the man
to become the professor that you see
that he is today, he had to trek, and
with joy. It was even an honor for him
that he could go to school.
But our generation today,
there are people who can have access You
can just walk 10 minutes, 20 minutes to
a church, and you will sit down and
follow online because of sheer laziness.
and then one
solid impartation to come upon you and
then God will trust you with the
destinies of men globally. It doesn't
work that way.
Hallelujah.
My dear people are here. Sometimes I go
online and I listen to their songs. When
I listen to their songs, I call them and
I say this thing you sang,
congratulations. From a spiritual
standpoint, I was touched, but from a
technical standpoint
this and this and this is a mistake. Go
and do it again. Go back to the studio.
Work again. Don't say I don't have
money.
The money you got as honorarium is not
for buying clothes. Go and invest in
your mind. The one for clothes will
come.
Go and invest in your mind.
Can I tell you there are many of you
right now what you have around you is
what has made your head empty because
the money God gave you was supposed to
be for your head. You denied your head
of an opportunity to be rich in
knowledge and you kept creating a
semblance of success whereas there was
nothing there. It is better for people
to know you have nothing physically, but
that they can appreciate the investment
of God's grace. How long did it take
Pharaoh to decorate Joseph?
They didn't decorate his mind.
Decorating your body can happen in one
day.
I know the cloth does not look very
nice, but you just invest in your spirit
and your mind. The day the person sent
to appreciate your value comes by God.
That person can take you shopping in one
day and buy your whole destiny for you.
Are we together?
I love that song. Prepare to sing it for
me.
Come, key strings.
Okay.
You just sing it one time for me. He
wrote the song. I want you to just sing
that song. It said It means fix me.
We're stepping into a prophetic
dimension in this teaching now. There
are some of you there are things you
need to throw away. Throw away and make
up your mind. Sing for me Kstrings.
Unworthy yes, my stay.
But love your love calls to me
and says
child be bold and come.
Oh, Father.
Here I am.
In some way
There is a house that song that says fix
me.
Is a cry walk on me.
What does it take
for my glory to rise? Fix me.
If it takes fasting, fix it oh God.
If it takes prayer, fix it oh God.
If it takes me going for trainings, fix
it oh God. If it takes another level of
education and knowledge, fix me oh God.
But by all means
by all means, I refuse to remain
ordinary.
By all means, I refuse to remain a
mediocre. By all means,
Hallelujah.